Guide to the Hiram Corson papers, 1842-1956.
Corson, Hiram papers, 1842-1956.
- Series VI. Photographs
  - Eugene Rollins Corson, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Eugene Rollins Corson and Hiram Corson together, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of House presented to the Corson's at Trinity College Commemoration, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Signed photograph of Walt Whitman, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Hiram, Caroline, and Eugene Corson, 1875-1903 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of x-rays, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Portrait photograph of Hiram Corson, 1902 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Formerly on display in the A.D. White library